<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Post on 10xdevjourney</title>
    <link>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/categories/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Post on 10xdevjourney</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 22:06:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0815Sailsman.github.io/categories/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Individual Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/posts/individual-cybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 22:06:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/posts/individual-cybersecurity/</guid>
      <description>small preamble about how this is just me talking right into the void its just a way to note a checklist to track what i still need to do
also, i didnt feel like formatting this one so fuck you future me
password management pw manager, use different, random passwords for everything
Backups (incl. offsite server) store important data (especially the pw database) on backup drives. setup a small offsite server (like a raspberry pi with a harddrive attached) as an offsite backup, so in case of fire or something that destroys your data at home you dont lose all your passwords / accounts also print out your pw db for exmample from time to time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What even is a 10x-Dev?</title>
      <link>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/posts/what-even-is-a-10xdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 21:41:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/posts/what-even-is-a-10xdev/</guid>
      <description>One of the reasons I am starting this blog is my interest in the concept of the 10x developer. Said to be ten times as efficient as their coworkers, these mystical creatures would be the pinnacle of modern software development, envied by their peers and searched for by hiring teams around the world.
So, the question I want to answer is: Is the concept of the 10x developer real or just that: A concept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 18:01:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://0815Sailsman.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>This is my first blog post!
To celebrate, here is a small tutorial how to print &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; to the console in Java!
public static void main(String[] args) { System.out.println(&amp;#34;Hello World&amp;#34;); } </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
